Hello hello if that bathroom channel keep
creating friends today's first video we
victim of the flats
look at all the important indicators and as
we saw in all the indicators and updates in this video right now the
market is going through a good
level of correction along with consolidation
a reed movement is going on
some of the indicators of duty are approaching their important technical
support levels
unmute again right now by purchasing some of its long-term
tractor labels and replacing the
talk bar from there so this quality can remain for a
few days hence
we feel that this is the time for less total acceptance and
chutney and a little quantity your
investment 12:00 Whenever you get a chance keep
replying keeping this news and
these figures in mind which
fundamentals stop remaining which pins can
Indians do for betting whatever
is available to you at good valuation and
which surprise milk you
can like that I will discuss in this video
So friends, if you haven't subscribed to my channel, then
do it now and
press the bell icon because we keep updating
our boss on a weekly basis like this
and keep doing it with you.
Chakli can be used a lot, so
taking in water tank, let's get
started friends, as we have been doing for the last two-three
years. In today's video
also, we are going to share so many staff officers
that I will not be able to give you the details of all the staff.
This video will become very
long, but the regular arrangement of our channel,
Mohit, will be very well aware of all the staff
because
we have definitely done the detailed review of all the staff in
some video in different pack channel lists on the channel.
Friends, in this
video with James Rate Today Price
on Star Plus, I will
also give a perfect introduction of all the staff for our neck tumor so
that you can get an idea of
what all the companies use and
why all these stock fundamentals are for long
term investment. Then I can type set
light jump right words. So friends, the
first companies of today's depression  Bajaj
Finance is a very strong and such a
good non-banking finance
corporation. Welcome after 50 minutes.
It belongs to the Bajaj Group and is a very good and
well-managed company. Its corporate
governance is good. At the same time, it is a
very strong
champion because of several factors that we have discussed in a
different support video. In this,
we talked about stocks in the banking and insurance sector,
so we talked about market performance in some detail.
And
soon I will bring a fundamental love
video on this, we will talk about it in more detail.
Why has Bajaj done such a moot business,
why is it such a stroke player in the
sector? So what should you do now? If you find it a
strong player, you find it a good spot,
but for long term investment, then the first
price level can be maintained in this way,
that 4547 is the middle level, the favorite safety
level. Second, if there is such a
big fall, because affected
Facebook wall sentiments, then 3537 level can also give very
attractive price level.
Long term investment in Bajaj.
Finance Next companies, part of the
multinational company Bata India, let's
talk about cameras. Its Indian subsidiary has a gift
business and is the market leader. It has a very good
search engine. Along with Relax,
another company I like is Pandey
's tweet segment Ajit Quality. When the stock was hit, it was
also hit very hard. There was a huge
decline and there has
n't been much recovery from there yet. You can
see that it is also around its March 2020
levels. Now you can see that
in mid-March, it was around the same level,
which is its level today. There has
n't been much recovery yet. And this has happened
because you know that Bata's
footwear statement comes, this tweet
comes, along with it, there is also a shift in their children going to school,
so all those shops have
not opened completely yet, the shops which were open themselves have
also started closing again. So
due to all those packs, this is causing
problems in Bata India and
after relieving its highest level, it has
fallen again.  This whole market is moving between the level of 13 to 14,
almost right now if it is
seen anywhere around the responsable level then
this temple is a good cause notice to protect
meeting Bate India in friends, if you
make a statement then the first press love can be around 13
to 14, why can there be many
moving averages, superintendents of this, the two end exc
for moving average is around 1450 monthly
and this is the
question from that, then many such stops do
not remain below half of the morning for very long, although since
Bata India is also perceptible because when
tweeting, soldiers survey
sentiments, then if you want to activate it in gas pricing, then
like this is not the
best price level, then extra attack
meeting water, but if you want to wait a little, then you
can add money from 12.5 to 13. If there is a little more decline, there is a
little more beating of the market, then you can
start doing extensive minutes at this level, but it is a very
strong company, G Road Company, good initiative  This
company has also become a leader in its sector. So, the
network of addresses of all these things, I see good growth potential in it for the
long term. So,
this one-stop different keeper, Nylon Audio,
long term investment, the next company is India
's best private sector company. And a
lot of fields and sentences have developed a little in it, due to which there is
some
pressure on the price. We had stopped its credit
card business campaign
because there are many technical glitches. So,
if you look at the opportunity of all these things,
you see long term questions in HDFC Bank.
Now, what should I tell you, HDFC Bank has been
such a good, such a big wealth creator in the
past. No matter how much you
say about it, it will seem less because it is a huge
wealth creator.
But the problem is that one company details in a
consistent compounder, the most assistant
commander debit the past, so let's say it will be very big,
so if you
want to start mining HDFC Bank, then
I think you can start clicking on 1415 bp whose current
price is around there.
If you
want to wait a little, you can also tweet 1213 rupees. There will be
such a huge fall, there
seems to be a little less chance of it in the stop,
but if it comes on that president, then
definitely next and very attractive
prices and you can start a meeting for
long term in HDFC Bank. The next company is also
equally good, its a sound hunter company. Both
these banks, the style of operations is a
little different like that of HDFC Bank and Kotak
Mahindra Bank, but both are very fundamentally sound
banks. If I
talk about two best banks in the private sector,
everything is positive, talk to two banks, the
parties are also in the ad and court matter, then you can
also see offers and sweets for updating Kotak Mahindra Bank.
You
can wait for 1718, it is its price, in
fact, very close, it is not very far, so this was it. In the
meantime, whenever you see it,
you
can like your tip in the face gradually. If you
want to wait a little on the investment capital, then wait for
14 and a half years, 2015.  You can
also increase the speed limit of professional
value and profession there,
you can see opportunities there and sports stars in these
and long term
investment in Kotak Mahindra Bank, the
fundamentals of the next company are very soft, these
companies belong to Procter & Gamble Group, let's go
behind and
talk about healthcare, these
multinational companies, everyone knows that it is quarter
and embellished, I said that it has
two-three subsidiaries in Indian Saras Dairy,
one of its subsidiaries is very happy, we are attached to one of its subsidiaries,
not the middle, but to talk about Gail,
click on it, go for sanitary napkins etc.,
they
consider it a business behind it, we are talking about that here, it is
going on behind that to do the
first problem can be between Rs 6000 to Rs 500,
which is around cigarette festival,
second preserve, we can update it,
if it comes on special then it will do quite
differently  The
company is debt-free. It belongs to a
large multinational group. So, it can
definitely add a very consistent
compounder. It will keep doing a good job on different issues. The
petition will be done by a travel
company. This box can be expected
for a long time. The next company,
which you might know better than naukri.com, is a
job line company. We are
talking about Information for India. It has
many businesses. Its
director, Managing Director Sanjeev
Mirchandani ji, is a very good winter capitalist. He has
incorporated many startups.
His business is very good.
I have identified many startups and has been a great
resource for acquiring knowledge. So, if you want to play a little
active involvement in the startup sector, if you
want to dip into that, then Eco Skin is good work.
They have a stake in Zomato of China.
Yes,
many startups keep doing this front
and they also used to do a lot of stocks. Being a good guru, they used to do
good group work. So,
I also set an alarm for Infosys regarding all these discussions.  If we talk about
IT and tech sector
stocks, then you can see some details about this question there too.
If you
look at the long-term potential in this, then
I think that you can start commissioning on the price of Titli Soch 144. The
mad level of the stock, which can be updated, is
3536 paise, it is much above that level right now,
but if it can move on that then definitely
your tasty margin will increase even more.
This is a small volume stock, it has some up and down
movement, but if it gives 7.5 on it, then
definitely you can make your profit.
22530 Foreign Investment in India.
Next company is not very strong player in the retail sector of India.
Abhinav
Supervisor is more known by the name of Kam Demand. There is
no need for me to tell much about it.
In the detail sector, it is a very strong, very
good motor business, debt free business. All of us have
beans shops here, which are
tasty, so they also do all the land,
so they do
not need much debt.  There is a significant increase in operating, the
inventory is
kept very streamlined, the inventory is
processed very fast, due to this they are
able to give good discounts as well,
due to which their detailed customer base also keeps
increasing significantly in EFE. Delhi
Chief Guest has given the quality, although it is
shown in profit numbers, but
clear the numbers of remaining revenue etc.
and in that they have shown good recovery in turmeric,
although but it is a
due to the increasing number of cases,
again the stock is looking a little low,
but for the long term, if you
can do this volatile and depression,
if you can fold this topic,
each unit can provide good
returns in the future, anyway the discussion,
then the demand has gone up significantly, if you
want to start regulating this topic, then
2764 850 edit price traveler of ₹100, you
can start admission at a price range time, you can wait for it in other crops, you
can maintain it but
150 Abe stock gets a little more pressure
because of any external number of office
top admissions on that campus and if in such an environment you can
start these innovative
supermodels next company engaged in tractor
India travel industry proper play is to be done a
little you think that travel and
tourism pass will be introduced police can very from place to place the
recovery of these
page industries I will talk about this
update free company almost free companies
very good remote companies well
connected to the market its sector so if you
want to start doing 5 minutes care friends if you think that recovery
play will be seen in poverty and Vikrampal again
recovery in the market then if
you want to play that then
care friends thank you very strong
candidate you can take the first price of 325 350 you can
keep an eye on this cup on the other hand you
can keep an eye on that
double point near 275 to 300 just printed VIP
Industries and this company is Whirlpool's
World Track International company UC company
its Indian subsidy  Rudrapur India
Map is talking about this web
is a good star player, debt free company,
motor business is a good market city, not only in
air conditioners but also in washing
machines, speech in recruitment refrigerators,
slip, how to regulate Whirlpool India, a company having a good market in the white goods sector, you
can save money with this, its desk movie is
around Everest, this price level,
you can definitely save success on this
and this is around the current price table, so
if you think this is a big tube, then
definitely important meeting Whirlpool
India for long term, but if you
want to wait a little, you think that there may be a little
more decline in the stock, then you
can invest in the festivals of 2020 to 21, you can
start your 1 million there,
next company has some space Vikram,
I don't discuss it much
usually, but since it is
available on good attractive festivals, hence I have included you in the list  The
companies in question are United Breweries, a United Spirits Group company, but Virat's operations are actually done by him.
I will tell you that half of
this list is under the name of McDougall's,
that company is separate. We are
talking about United Breweries,
but it belongs to a good group.
DJ Blueprint is a very good group.
Its team management is very good and its
corporate governance is very sound. So if
you want to play this, if you
feel that the consumption of beer etc.
can increase, then when you can take these decisions, then you can take
a look at United Breweries.
So if you
want to invest in it, then you can fit the level of 11 to 1150.
Its current price
is in between the change, so definitely you can
start digging into them instead of
long-term technical. If you want to wait a little, if
you think that Kuwait's interest will
increase, then during this time, there can be a
profit in the video.
This is a little for a minute.  You can wait
and update the price between 900 and 1000
and you can next it there. The
next companies are free friends
multinational pharmaceutical company, its
Indian subsidiary North India, we are talking on camera, to do
it for 1 minute, first press
tables Sector-75, second one is 786, in such a situation you
can wait for it, mouth 7077, Saka Chaman to
Zauq is a very good brand of
pharmaceutical industry, its
dividend history is very good, it does very
good turmeric on different, it
is a good company for long term investment,
so fundamentally
very soft companies, there is
no need to worry, if you want to invest
in fennel for different, you should also do different,
sorry for that,
Faiz Akram is going to do it immediately,
but all four fair and generation companies can
also be very good and all three of which are
pharmaceutical industry, so a lot of
defense staff can now
for difference stock allocation, next committee back
multinational  It's a pharmaceutical company, but with
more growth and intestines. Then, let's
figure that when we talk about this, there's a little
difference. Stocks do good
on the president, but if
you look at it in terms of growth, you can see that the first step is the growth
story. Growth is a topic, and to invest in it,
I think it's
quite good.
What is 15,000 from there? Now you can see that its
Twenty20 target, which is possible, is
around 15,000. So, this company has its own
stock price. If you get it at 15,000
without a desk test, then it will definitely start coming out.
If you want to wait, you
can wait for 13,000 to 14,000.
Although, definitely, there's nothing above the label yet,
but if it goes anywhere near that range,
this top difference is where you can
locate the best company for long-term
investment. The next company is Pipe
Unprecedented. We discussed this in a little more detail
when we discussed Best of
Foreign investment in infrastructure
sector was described, so we had described retail
policy in a little more detail for medicine, so
if you see a little long competition in 1 liter of water, it is a
very good initiative, garment
company, this is also an almost free company, well
garment company, it has given very good rates, so if you will do a lot of
details,
fundamentals of great, then
you will see a lot of good strip and on the best
of fundamental research, if you want to invest in tehsils, then you can
fit the level of 15 to 50, it is
around this year, just a little more, if there is a
correction in it, then it can definitely be a very
strong candidate for long term
investment on that share, but if you
want to wait a little, then you can do 12.5 to 13 and
petrol with less VAT, that is also a very
good attractive price label and its
200, its movie brush is also
from the place of 12 sugar level, so if this top
falls to that level, it falls till now, then
definitely you can talk meeting
place  Polytechnic for long term next
company is related to banking sector
but if I talk then best
friends I have already talked about
HDFC Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank,
both of these are my favorite banks but the
history of Axis Bank has not been very good
but their management current
management is quite good Amitabh ji
Shankar, Managing Director, his history is
very good, this tailoring Monu had done a very
good job, so I think that
in future Axis Bank may cool down a bit
that friends, there are petty issues related
issues, that may be a little dress, there may be
dress arrangement Vikram Thakur
10th August 4 If we talk about private sector from bank
and
press of strong private sector bank DSC Kotak Mahindra
Axis Arise, these four banks
seem good to me if we talk about big banks and
as I talked about in today's first video, there was
vitamin A discussion of IDFC First Bank,
so in this video I
talked about Play Vaidyanathan ji in it, so if we
track all these points then that
feature investment is one of those banks  Axis
Bank has seen a significant correction
from its all-time high price, so
if you want to activate, you
can tweet about the price of 625-675. Similarly,
around the time of delivery, the arrangement for separation on which you can
keep your balance is 5.5 to
6.5 bbl. The next threat like No. is already
talking a little about Father, this too has made
a mountain of possible gains, it
is a company doing good Golden Ratio and
if you look at the long-term potential in this, then
4345 Chapra is the
first thing these people have talked about many
times on this channel,
many of you have also talked about the No. 1 price in it, what will be the anniversary in it,
SpiceJet has gone up a bit according to that and has gone to
4865,
but if there is a slight decline again
in it, some consolidation is seen, then you
can update on this decision and
come and meet on this decision, you can start,
if you have not already done it, other
fashions, you can wait for that much
decline.  Usually, in pharma stocks, the
app comes in defense staff, but
if there is that much decline, then they should do
41 daily 39518 clothes. You can update all this
and come there and if you can do such a mission, then the
next companies can be fair.
India's largest player in gold loan finance is
Motor Finance.
We have discussed this in previous videos.
I think Muthoot Finance is
India's largest and one of the strongest
players in gold finance.
Muthoot Finance is a better company than Mannapuram Finance because
of certain business, which is Motor Finance, which is only
in gold loans, whereas Mannapuram Finance
does other things as well, and all their
things are not that big. So, if you
want to play only in the gold finance sector and
if you see long-term potential in it, then
Muthoot Finance scam BJP and play on
gold finance in India. To do this topic for 1 minute, the
first prices reached
1112 rupees. In which we have seen
that it has consolidated many times on this earth,
we had talked about it last week also and at
that time  It is available in that range, now it
is a little above, if there is a little correction of three,
four, five percent, then it will again
come in this price range and
you can chart its union at the level of 11 to 12,
if you feel that
since the gold price is down, then there can be a little more
pressure in it, why at the top.  Because as
you know, as its prices go up,
Muthoot Finance will benefit. Its prices go
up because there has been some problem in the gold crop. The
download page has
remained. There has been selling pressure for some
days and some months. So, as
you can see, motor finance has been
consolidating for many months. There has been
consolidation in motor finance for about six to eight months. Just
like there was consolidation in gold, there was
consolidation in motor finance as well. So,
if you feel that there may be
some more pressure in the stock, then you
can update from 1000 to 11 April. The next
company is in front part manufacturing, from
there, like if there is infection
in electrical electronics, then
we are talking about United One, one of the largest number congress players in India, Addiction Technologies. In this, the stock had a split with
due to which the top had gone up to a very high level. From
there, there will be a slight correction to a good level. There will be
some consolidation
in the stop. So, I think if you
want to wait a little at 3233 and a half, then
you will get an update on that in the table.  You can do this, you
can start Kamlesh there, the second
festival where its moving
average speed is 200, that is 2560 27 fourth level,
if you can update the deceased from that,
if it comes on this channel, then you are
seeing that for many months, whenever there was any
concern, after that it
supported the TDS boys and the maximum this
feature has dropped, so we are
supported on a moving average of one and a half and its currency which
I sent Rahan Day Spa is around 369, so
best for your comfort send notice
perception and stop, whichever of these two is more
suitable for the problem, flop more
comfortable feel, you can start its 1
million there, the next
gas distribution company is my
favorite Mahanagar Gas
which is operational in Maharashtra Mumbai adjoining
areas, through this you can add VAT of Rs. 1000 from
11 April onwards, a little
and if there is a correction in this, then
you can calculate its current price from this there  But you
can do that festival definitions, on the
other hand, in such a situation, you can wait for that
festival of 900 to 1000. Now this company
is a giant company in the general insurance
sector, India's largest private general insurance company,
Android Lombard General Insurance. To
invest in this topic,
six and a half inches of cloth from you, before this, it is a good
attractive possibility. We
can see consolidation at 40 for a long time. The
moving average of the desk is also around 1413 sixes-fours press
level. The second reserve, where there is a
good price level, there is a good support
level, that is 1213, but it is light, but
I think that from these two, in whichever
comfort level you have, wherever you are comfortable, you can
start admission there.
This is a very strong company, battery, computer,
insurance is a weakness or 307, its
nut is quite good. You can talk about its foot,
when I will give its dedicated video,
then we will only talk about it, there were tricks,
how is its top end profit and
all things in a dedicated video.  For
now, if you
want to note down the press day, you can try using these two
companies.
My favorite company from the placement company is HDFC
AMC. It has a very big market. It has one of the
largest and largest cities in India. It has grown
with SBI Mutual Fund.
HDFC Mutual Fund owns asset
management companies in India. To do this, you can tweet the top 5
minutes of the press meet at 2728. There
is a moving average of two remedies there and if it supports you there, then
I think that is a
good support level. At that time,
related to HDFC AMC, all the gift no
toilet universities company, other preserves can be
updated. Although that
price level is quite below that, there is
little chance of it falling till there.
But if such a fall happens, then
24:30 to 5:30 April will be very attractive and
long term investment and fundamentally sound
companies like HDFC
AMC are leading companies, hence Sanyam C's
parade and
only SDMC's HDFC
Bank, HDFC Life, HDFC Ergo, all these
apps  The group meeting is of its paint
company and also of India's visible
housing finance company HDFC Ltd
and Singh Development Finance Corporation of
India. HDFC Ltd is describing
it as a mildly inefficient company at 2425 to regulate it. It
is a good fundamentally sound company and
on good probation, you should tick on it directly. This is
not very high because it is a
holding company. The valuation of ULIP is a
little low for holding companies, but it is
not only a holding company, it is a
housing finance company in itself, so you have to keep this in
mind. This is a standalone company, this company
also has a standalone business and at the same time
it is a holding company.
Many of its test companies have life discussed,
so the first one is of 24 to 25, before this the second one
is special support, that is, of 2223 for
investment in HDFC Ltd. The next
stock is Eicher Motors India, a
leading Indian company manufacturing two-wheeler motorcycles ranging from Rs. 240 to Rs. Royal,
not because the brand is Eicher Motors
and it makes only two-wheelers, it makes four-wheeler
commercial vehicles in collaboration
with JOG.  Their performance and it
makes commercial vehicles are very good. There are
many good brands like
Royal Enfield and
many more. Friends, you have many motorcycles
as well as different Galaxy series. So to
invest in Eicher Motors, I think
that the price of 24 @ 100% Black should be taken first,
which is quite attractive. Secondly, you
can keep such a register. One, the
middle of this is definitely backed by a very
attractive price. At that time, litigation
motors, Sage Immortality Invest, very
strong companies, tax-free companies,
good operations, retail business is very good.
And friend request, it is a very mooted
business. So definitely I think that the
first year long term potential is Edison
Motors J2 Price LMB Captain John and
you will feel more comfortable in both these wires mosque,
from there you can start your eye
relation with your investment.
These are Sharm Motors Ajay, our
next and last company of depression is Maruti
Suzuki India Limited, I
need to tell you a lot about you. You know that
more than fifty percent of the market  Apart from this, Tata
Motors and Honda are growing at a good pace even without Honda,
especially Hyundai's
sales are growing well, Tata Motors'
electric vehicle sales are increasing
and Maruti Suzuki is a little late in
electrification, but if seen from the long-term
potential, their
electric vehicle production has also started
and its market is so good,
script and regulation is so good, Maruti
Suzuki's spare parts are
available so easily,
general brand
awareness of perception has been established,
this is definitely within the topic
and Maruti Suzuki is a brand that people trust a lot,
hence I think that this
company has a lot of potential for long
term investment, debt free companies,
operations were quite good, writ petitions were quite
good of this company, so I think that
668 and a half is the first part of sure, we
can make this proposal, we can
start oxidation, second pressure can be reduced
there of 158 reminders.  Also, with a good support level, the
mission can come there and if in such a case,
60 can be done Maruti Suzuki India
Limited, so I hope friends,
we have tried to cover so many Josh Talks here, we have made
their discussion points, so
you will benefit from all these
descriptions, you will also get some prints
which will benefit you, your long term
investment journey, fight ho front, best
dialogues in sports, beneficial to you
in your long term investment process,
friends, today's video cassette, which is
Knowledge Power Screen, is the mission of this channel, which is to
bring the right knowledge to you,
in the upcoming new videos, we will discuss many interesting
topics and I will keep
bringing user guide user topics for you,
similarly, we will keep discussing weekly market updates and
our views about the market situation, so
definitely
subscribe to our channel, Women to the Father
of If you liked today's video content, then
like the video, if you think that
this information can help someone, then share it with
your friends and family members
Share with and subscribe to the channel. We will see you
in our next video and
with coffee discussion till then take care see you soon.